In this tutorial video, we use the 11th version of DOS Marvelous Designer.
If you need to learn the 10th version of Marvelous Designer, please watch the previous video.
In order to learn more about the DOS Marvelous Designer, you can find the Modular Configurator in the title of the window.
In the Modular Configurator, there are various types of preset costumes, such as T-shirts, shirts, jackets, etc.
These costume presets are called modules, and they are made up of basic costume models.
You can use them as a basis to modify into the costume you need.
Please note that certain modules are made based on certain virtual models.
In this tutorial video, you will learn how to import a T-shirt module.
First, we need to import a virtual model.
I will import Feifei from the Female VR folder as a virtual model.
Before using the module compiler, please make sure your virtual model is in a upright position.
Double-click the POS folder and double-click the A-POS.
In this position, the arm will be placed on both sides of the body.
Then click on the title of the window in the library and switch to the Modular Configurator in the drop-down menu.
In the Modular Configurator, you will see all the default modules that Marvelous Designer has.
Next, select the module category.
Here we double-click to open the Women folder.
In the Women folder, there are all kinds of clothing modules that female virtual models can use.
Select the T-shirt folder, you will see that there are two T-shirts options here.
These two are divided by the sleeves.
The first one is the shoulder sleeve, and the second one is the normal sleeve.
Here we choose the Selling, which is the normal sleeve type.
The module type will be divided by row.
There are two modules in the T-shirt.
The sleeve module and the collar module.
Now let's take a closer look at the 2D window.
All the clothing modules in the Modular Configurator have a module frame on the outside.
These modules are related to the Frenzy line, so you don't need to create more Frenzy lines.
Finally, you can press the control key to simulate the T-shirt on the virtual model.
Then we can learn how to modify the module version.
As shown in the video, you can use the edit version tool to adjust the module version.
When you edit the module version, the module frame will also modify its shape and Frenzy line.
Using the modules in the Modular Configurator will help you quickly build up all kinds of basic clothing.
You can rely on them to create your own work.
This series of fast learning videos ends here.
Welcome to watch other tutorials.